all right so today is actually a very
important day to me we're going to meet
up with Ricky which is one of my first
students that I ever had about two and a
half years ago and I appreciate this guy
like you guys have no idea because he
put his trust in me when it comes to
educating and then fast forward two
years later he's profitable he's made
almost six figures in trading and we're
going to do a podcast today with him but
before we do the podcast we are going to
you know have like a little day together
we're going to go eat uh just kind of
get to know each other right before the
podcast cuz it's just better so the
conversations they just are more fluent
um so we're going to go pick up Ricky we
flew him out to Miami from Arizona I'm
excited to meet him yo you guys ready
for this co- start you
ready never get all right so today the
weather in Miami little shitty but we
are pulling up right now to Ricky uh
Ricky you're going to see this obviously
in the future I'm more nervous than you
are brother cuz you're the first guy
that trusted in me so appreciate you bro
so we're pulling up right now what's
good dog yeah bro crazy to meet you good
dog good it's [__] I'm tripping right
now yo so this has been my virtual
friend for like what like two years
almost right yeah bro a little bit over
two years over two years bro yeah was in
the first boot camp I know I know for
the OG how was uh how was the flight it
was good dog it was real good uh super
smooth uh obviously a little delay but
other than that bro everything's been
super this your first time in Miami or
no uh yeah very first time yeah well you
got he got a little taste of the Miami
weather so earlier today what did you
get it was in the morning it was like
sunshine everything was cool and then
out of nowhere I I go like downstairs we
eat go back upstairs and then I get a
tornado warning and I'm like what like I
was tripping and now we're good again
yeah now we're good yeah feels good out
here for those you guys don't know I
just got back from Columbia yesterday I
got back at 5: so I had to pretty much
set everything up get everything
organized
bro yeah it's crazy something else so I
mean you you ate earlier you're probably
hungry now right so let's go at one of
my favorite spots all right I pretty
much eat there like every day and then I
have a gift for you at the house bro oh
[__] oh
[__] it's just fast bro this [__] is
live fast it is super
[__] we're about to get on a chase
right now you better not get a Chase all
right ready
go you're
good
oh you want to know what's crazy this
car breaks more than like it goes fast
god
damn this is
crazy yo tell me the videos don't do the
Justice bro like no justice bro like if
you don't see this in person bro this
[__] is crazy wait I have a gift for you
I have a gift for you at the house it's
a it's a personal gift yeah the rapping
is not that nice you know I'm a guy I
wrapped it myself bro I do the same
thing I try to rap some [__] I can't do
it no no you're going to laugh at the
rapping it's actually it's actually
hilarious I'm excited bro I think I
think gifts are are to be something when
it comes like not of value but of like
meaning behind it so I like you know I
can give you like a [__] Gucci or
some [__] right right right exactly but
that that doesn't do anything you know
you know what's funny bro is me and Mike
were talking about that and he was like
he's like it's crazy because I don't
know another Trader in the industry that
not only gives away sauce like Alex does
but also is willing to do stuff with and
for his students the way you do and he
was like it's crazy because me and him
were talking like brainstorming I was
like you know be fire in the future like
we know Alex has everything and
everything he needs like he don't need
anybody to do anything for him but what
be fire is like we me and him plan like
a personal trip like with you in the
near future like obviously later on
right from the prophets that you guys
that you have taught us you know what
I'm saying and he was like we could like
we could buy Alex a watch we could buy
Alex some [__] you know what I mean he's
like but from the from the personal
aspect it's it's different when you get
like a gift like that you know what I'm
saying like it's it means more than just
oh like here's a Gucci bag you know like
you can do you can do that any day yeah
no that's that it's just different I
like that that you guys are thinking
like that cuz obviously you you know you
guys have a different state of mind and
almost to become a profitable Trader you
kind of have to have a different people
don't understand they don't bro they
don't like that's what I'm saying like I
can't like I'm I mean I've been on a few
podcasts like obviously in San Antonio
with real estate involved in stuff but
like I I love to talk about that stuff
because I have a lot of a lot of
knowledge that I Can Shed from when I
first met you to now like the the
different mindset like you talk about
the aha moment right like there's a
bunch of stuff that I I just I can't
wait to just share my experience and
stuff bro so this is one of my favorite
spots okay it's called diced okay it's
like a healthier alternative than chip
okay I see that really healthy so so
it's funny right like of course we'll
talk about it later in the podcast I'm
just [__] I've been waiting to meet
you for a long [__] time but um there
so my all my family right like my
in-laws my wife and everything like
they've seen everything kind of
transpire nobody understands what
trading is right I try to trying to
explain to my wife what a [__]
Candlestick is and [__]
yeah that goes on a cake like so so dog
it's crazy because like I I talked to
them about it and like we're talking
about coming on a trip right and my
father-in-law was like are you sure like
you know what I'm saying I'm like yeah
like I am sure you know but then like
they started giving me doubts and I'm
like who the [__] Alex like why would he
you know what like start like my was
everywh yeah it was crazy but I don't
know if I'm feeling another 30 day bro
the 30 the 30 day probably was brutal
for you yeah bro I know it was and I
like I I just know and I appreciate your
dedication cuz I know that you have a
lot going on and it was it's crazy
because you were there every damn day
bro and I just know like there even if
you switched up times you were like hey
look might be like 2 hours late but I'm
going pull up I'll let you guys know
yeah no matter how late it is I'll be
there you know and I was like d yeah I
don't I I don't know if I still got that
in me right now I know bro like bro I'm
saying like you got a lot I might do it
cuz I i' a lot of new Traders are coming
in now yeah yeah yeah and I I bro I just
I I want to just make it all one shot
make it very simple but and I feel like
I can make it more effective cuz bro
that last one I that [__] was draining
bro it was not it wasn't even worth the
money bro like that [__] was gone like
next week you know what I mean it's not
M it's not worth it bro but I don't know
if I do it no I'm going to do it if I do
it I'm going to do it like the better
and improvs for sure I think I think for
you it just has to make like it just has
to be if you have it in you right like
cuz that's what you have to tell
yourself and convince yourself like man
do I really want to do that because like
you said the money probably not worth it
right now you know but it but like for
me like this is worth it yeah yeah yeah
this is lit know I me it's live it's
super live it'll be lit a year and a
half from now when another Ricky pulls
up you know what I mean like that's
where I'm like all right like that's
worth that's fire bro I remember at the
beginning when we got into the boot camp
this guy was in denial of my age cuz
you're how how old 32 and I'm
23 and then he was like bro there's no
way I'm taking advice from a
23y and I was like brother let me tell
you the the best advice I could have
taken was from a [__] 23 old it was
crazy it was crazy I remember that
vividly because you were on the zoom
call and I would let you know the
students talk and they boot camp he's
like yo but hold on hold on before I say
anything I can't [__] believe I'm
taking advice from you
bro it's a trip dog can't like I just
can't believe that I was 21 then yeah I
was 21 yeah you were 21 so that's what I
said I was like there's no way when he
first told me I was like get the [__]
out of you there's no way so first I
mean you just carry
yourself more grown like you just the
mindset is different bro for sure it's a
blessing m i remember that day you what
look at the weather how I know dud was
like [__] we just had a tornado
warning earlier I know now we're good to
go let's go over here now you now you
drive get the [__] out of here bro here
bro are you serious or you [__] with
me no here bro take it for real yeah
don't drop it in the hole right there
take it for real yeah let's go dog
what how do you put this thing in
drive is all just trying to figure it
out like see hold on hold on see open
the flap and then press the button this
no no no on the red flap this one and
then press the button press what button
that one that turn that b
off I was about to turn this [__] off
all right so you you want to put it in
Drive yes all right so just put the foot
on the brake okay that's it that's
enough so where are we going my house
how do we get there you don't know how
to get there
all right it right floor floor floor
floor floor oh hell no bro yeah man
forget man this is crazy dog I got you a
gift oh [__] is that the rapping right
there bro is that what you're talking
about that was the rapping yeah so this
is the raing I was about to ask you like
what the hell are you doing here looks
like a Halloween party went down you
just tore it down bro like I was telling
you earlier I think gifts are better
when they have a meaning behind it you
know not value behind it so this right
here the rapping has no value but
there's meaning the inside of the
rapping you know what I mean so again
bro appreciate you appreciate you having
me trusting me as being one of my first
students so I got you this right here
you can unra let me unra he just wrapped
it in uh and caution tap let's see oh
dude I would not go that route that's
going to take yeah just just [__]
tear it right hold on yeah here we go oh
there you go there we go there you go W
here it is we are so it's your very own
set for bro your very on set and
forget look at that [__] yeah there you
go see on set and forget that's fire bro
so obviously I could have gotten you
know something bigger I don't know I
don't know the sizing proportion of it's
good or bad so you know you put that up
bro and appreciate you dog that's fire
this is the same one that I have on my
office bro that I had for years that's
OG [__] bro that's OG [__] that's fire
bro oh oh okay oh yeah we just got this
new shotgun that's tight D what about
the uh
what about the the other T sent me a
picture earlier and he's like oh I'm
just chilling there's a [__] AR and a
pump and I'm like all right cool that's
my room I guess just chilling with that
[__] there like this is tight look so
this is my this is like the drift car
door oh yeah so the guy that I sold it
to like yo where's the door and I'm like
I don't know yeah I lost that [__] it's
on your wall right it's on my wall so
this is where I play poker and then this
computer right here this is the one
where actually the 30-day boot camp was
was hosted on so this is here because
this is the first computer I know it was
I know I remember you look I remember
these little things have been on here
for like 2 3 Years bro that's crazy we
want you want to know what's crazy
though like this is the first computer I
made a million dollars on so it's there
and then this is the first computer I
made 100K on hold on I got to get the
[__] I'm forget I'm recording hold on
wait wait this is [__] crazy so this
is from the original 30-day boot yeah
first Mill was made on that one first
mill on this one and then 100K on that
one up there
that's crazy bro yeah that's nuts and
then this this is my first letter that I
got from a student by Omar oh that's
tight yeah sorry brother I don't know
where you are right now dude but I hope
you're good that's tight so Omar you
know wrote this letter to me you know he
say he's my role model that's tight bro
so yeah I have it here as well that's
crazy so Omar have you seen this that's
nuts you're still you're still with me
brother yeah all the time I remember you
putting that [__] $5 to cover the
thing too yeah cuz be watching you me
you shoot bow and arrow no we're going
to shoot through this [__] wall right
now you Ain going to shoot that [__]
dude I bet you won't oh my God why does
this why does this guy do this to me bro
why is this guy doing this you're not
going to do
it he [__] did look at this [__] it's
in there you're [__] crazy bro leave
that that's part of the that's part of
the decor now no that's that's going to
stay right there now D what what uh what
were you telling Alex yeah no I'm just
saying man it's I think it's super big
that that Alex creating this experience
for us and like I said I'm not even
there but I feel like I'm
there I was telling all my boys I'm like
bro going to come back different bro
he's going to see you know we we're over
here we looking at Corvette and we're
like you know what I mean and I'm like
my boy going to go he's going to see
Lambo he's going to see roll Roy he's
going to see Miami he's going to see a
whole different type of stuff and his
vision is going to be different when he
comes back's come back
different's doing right now is where our
boundaries are he's picking up the
boundaries and he's setting them further
yeah and he's going to come back and
he's going to be like all right this is
where our boundaries were now this is
where they are going to be you're just
pushing the limit for all of us that's
hey and and it was and it was all it was
all possible because of a 23y old bro
it's freaking
crazy I'm
29 you know what I mean yeah I get I
sell cars and I get excited and I make
10K a month yeah and I get excited
because of that but to other people I
hear people say oh bro no no that's
expensive I'm like bro it's expensive to
us yeah other people it's a mindset at
the end of the day you% yeah and uh I
just feel like like bro you creating
this opportunity to take Rick out there
bro you don't know how many of us back
here at home are like dog what's Rick
[Laughter]
doing I had to keep it I had to keep it
high class bro for real like I I had
right I didn't tell I didn't really tell
anybody
right no no no yeah yeah hey the whole
time we were like kind of like just a
little doubtful I'm like bro I'm telling
Rick I'm like bro you don't even realize
how real this is and you're over there
right now but I don't think you
understand the situation that you're in
right now he's he's texting me he's like
bro this is it's unreal like it's a trip
bro I just wanted to FaceTime you bro I
was I just asked him that what for sure
and just on of everybody else man just
want to tell Alex man appreciate you
taking my boy out there cuz it's gonna
he's going to come back and set a fire
for each and every single one of us so
hey I haven't bought your course but I'm
one of your grand students cuz I'm Rick
student
I'm one of your grand
students he he's my grand
teer yeah hey he's passing you just be
passing the torch bro all right
appreciate youo appreciate you brother
see you man see you man okay sounds good
bro see you
later how does it feel to own one of
these bro honestly like how do you feel
like real like bro honestly first of all
I can't believe I paid 300K for this
[__] this is 300,000 [__] [__] and
then ballet still won't even ballet cuz
they they don't they don't know what it
is it's [__] annoying so it's more
like a car Enthusiast car yeah but it
feels amazing cuz this is fun
yeah die I keep CJ
oh [__] CU I didn't turn off traction oh
it stopped it that rookie
[Music]
mistake
[Applause]
so he didn't expect those driving
skills that sh was wild I mean the
videos don't do the Justice bro not at
all it's it's a whole different
experience a whole different vibe is
Alex is [__] crazy let me tell you
Alex is crazy n but good driver though
damn good driver what do you take on
from like this small experience from cuz
we still have to go back and do the
podcast like what what do you take on
like this small experience honestly bro
the the boundaries were already wide but
coming over here and actually me and you
in person first and foremost and just
getting you know seeing your lifestyle
seeing how you do things seeing
everything that you've earned is is just
super motivation so yeah bro from this
experience I just bro L lit me on fire I
just want to like I just want to [__]
set and forget you know what I mean like
that's all I want to do is just set and
forget bro for those you guys that don't
know what sudden and forget is that is
the strategy that has got Ricky here has
got has got me here to know all the toys
and all this fun stuff you guys want to
know more about it just click the link
in the description below we have proven
testimon right here that it works so
Ricky appreciate you brother appreciate
you you guys want to check out his story
the full story click the link below his
podcast will be there as well let's
check it